Raul H. Castro papers, 1903-2007 (bulk 1939-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 4: Law Practice Files, 1953-2004 (bulk 1980-2003)
  - National Institute of Former Governors. 1990 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Norma Nistor Murder Trial. 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 41-42)
  - Nogales City Charter Reform Referendum. 2000 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Petit, Preble. 1993 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Phelps Dodge Corporation. 1986 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Pima County Superior Court 1985 Annual Report. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Ramirez, Mauro. 1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Red Mass (Diocese of Phoenix). 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Roladex A-C. undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Roladex D-L. undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Roladex D-L. undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Roladex M-Q. undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Roladex R-T. undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Roladex U-Z. undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Salvadoran Asylum Case (Affidavit Request). 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - State Bar of Arizona. 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - State of Arizona Marriage Handbook. 2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - State Sentencing and Parity Review Study Committee. 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11-15)
  - Taking a Sonoran Declaracíon in an American Court. 1997 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1986 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19-24)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2-13)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1989 (Box 10, Folder 15-19)
  - Telephone Memo Records. 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - Tohono O'Odham Nation. 2002 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Trial Reporter of Southern Arizona. 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - United States Department of State Publications. 1984-1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Walsh and Levine. 1978-1983 (Box 11, Folder 6-7)
  - Water Rights. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Series 5: Subject Files, 1949-2005 (bulk 1971-1987)
  This series contains materials related to Castro's diplomatic career, speeches (including drafts and final versions), and material related to speeches (including magazine clippings, copies of others' speeches, and books). The series also contains several transcripts of biographical interviews given by Raul H. Castro. Some items are in Spanish. (Note: a subject files folder is located in Series 11: Oversized).
  - Ambassadorship to Argentina. 1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ambassadorship to El Salvador. 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bolles, Don. 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Botantes en Eleccíon General Nov. 2 de 1954. 1954 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Business Cards - Miscellaneous. undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Carter Administration Conflict of Interest Questionnaire. undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ceremonies Installing the Honorable Raul H. Castro, Judge. 1959 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Churchill, Winston. 1965-1975 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Citizen Band Radio Station Permit. 1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Diplomatic Calling Cards. undated (Box 11, Folder 19-22)
  - Dogs. 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - F-4 Phantom Flight (Luke Air Force Base). 1975 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Guest Book - Unidentified. undated (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Horses. 1971-1977 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Invitation - Presidential Inauguration of Ronald Wilson Reagan (Commemorative Invitation). 1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Johnson, Lyndon (Castro's Remembrances - News Clippings). 1973 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Manuscript - Recollections of the Hon. Raul H. Castro. 2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Oral History Interview Transcript - Democratic Party History Project. 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Oral History Interview Transcript - Lyndon Baines Johnson Library. 1971 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Pamphlets - Discurso Pronunciado Por El Ciudadano Presidente Jacobo Arbenz Guzman (Guatemala). 1953 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Pamphlets - Instituto Di Tella (Buenos Aires, Argentina). undated (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Panama Canal. 1978 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Presidential Inauguration of Lyndon Baines Johnson (Official Inaugural Program). 1965 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - The Raul H. Castro Institute (Arizona State University). 2005 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Relaciones Politicas Entre E.E.U.U. y Argentina Entre 1945 y 1978. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Speech Material. undated (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Speech Material. 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Speech Material. 1979 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Speech Material. 1980 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Speech Material. 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Speech Material. 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Speech Material. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Speech Material. 1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Speech Material. 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Speech Material. 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Speech Material (Doing Business in Argentina). 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Speech Material. (The World's Greatest Speeches). 1949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Speeches. undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Speeches. 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Series 6: News Clippings 1951-2000 (bulk 1974-1980)
  This series contains some news clippings from the 1950s regarding the Castro's "El Milagro" pony farm in Tucson. Also, there are clippings that document each new position in Raul H. Castro's public career. The series includes extensive clippings related to the 1970 and 1974 gubernatorial campaigns as well as clippings documenting Castro's governorship from 1974 to 1977. Of particular note are folders of clippings related to the investigation of the 1976 bombing death of Arizona Republic reporter Don Bolles. Several clippings from the 1990s and 2000s sum up Raul H. Castro's life and career. Some news clippings are in Spanish. (Note: some folders of oversized news clippings are located in Series 11: Oversized).
  - Bolles, Don. 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 11-14)
  - Falklands Crisis. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - General. undated (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
  - General. 1951-1958 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - General. 1960-1969 (Box 12, Folder 20-21)
  - General. 1970 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - General. 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - General. 1974 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - General. 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - General. 1975 (Box 13, Folder 3-21)
  - General. 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - General. 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2-18)
  - General. 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - General. 1977 (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
  - General. 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
  - General. 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
  - General. 1990-1999 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Nogales Charter Reform. 2000 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Pulliam, E. C. 1975 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Series 7: Photographic Material, 1939-2003 (bulk undated)
  This series is divided into four subseries. The Photo Albums subseries (1977; bulk undated) contains two albums of photographs taken on a trip to the North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) center at Cheyenne Mountain, Colorado. Photo Albums also contains an undated album of photographs of Ambassador Castro's official visit to a city in Argentina. The Photographs subseries (1939-2003; bulk undated) makes up the bulk of the Photographic Material series. It contains an assortment of photographs concerning different aspects of Raul Castro's career. There are photographs taken during his three ambassadorships. In particular, the subseries contains photographs documenting President Lyndon B. Johnson's and Lady Bird Johnson's visit to El Salvador in 1968 (the Castros hosted this visit). There are many photographs taken during Raul Castro's governorship of Arizona, including several official photographic portraits. The subseries also contains many family photographs as well as photographs of political, entertainment, and sports celebrities such as Jimmy Carter (with Raul Castro; inscribed), Clint Eastwood (with Raul Castro), Clint Eastwood (with Patricia Castro; inscribed), Charlton Heston (with Raul Castro), Ginger Rogers, and Olympian Jesse Owens (inscribed). The Negatives subseries contains family images (including Raul Castro's birthplace) as well as images of a trip through the Andes mountains of South America. The Slides subseries contains images of the U.S.S. Arizona Memorial dedication festivities. (Note: some folders of oversized photographs are located in Series 11: Oversized).
  - Subseries: Photo Albums, 1977
    - Gobierno de la Provincia del Chaco. undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - NORAD Dinner. 1977 (Box 15, Folder 16-17)
  - Subseries: Photographs, 1939-2003
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Ambassador's Body Guards. 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Ambassador's Residence Furniture. undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; American Club Year-end Reunion. 1978 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Andes Village Scenes. undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Benson, Ezra T. (LDS Church President). 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Braniff Airlines Stewardess Graduation. 1979 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; General. undated (Box 15, Folder 24-26)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; General. 1975 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Ambassadorships,- Argentina; General. 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Honorary Degree from John Kennedy University. 1978 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Municipalidad de Quilmes. 1979 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Rogers, Ginger. 1980 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Swearing- In Ceremony. 1977 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Teatro Colón. undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; United States Embassy. undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Yacht Trip. 1977 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Yacht Trip. 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Yacht Trip ( Steiner, Veronica). 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; Barrientos, Rene (Bolivian President). undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; Candia, Alfredo Ovando (General). 1968 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; General. undated (Box 16, Folder 4-6)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; General. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; General. 1969 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; Press Conference (La Paz). undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ambassadorships- Bolivia; Swearing-In Ceremony. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; Ambassador's Residence. undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; Ambassador's Residence. 1966-1969 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; Earthquake Relief from U.S. 1965 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. undated (Box 16, Folder 15-22)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. 1965 (Box 16, Folder 23-24)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. 1966 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. 1967 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; Presentation of Credentials to President Julio Rivera. 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; President Johnson Family Photograph. 1967 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; President Johnson's Visit. 1968 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Family Photographs; Castro Birthplace. undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Family Photographs; Castro, Nacho. 1992 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Family Photographs; Castro, Raul. undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Family Photographs; Castro, Raul. undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Family Photographs; General. undated (Box 17, Folder 2-5)
    - Family Photographs; General. 1939-1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Governorship; Arizona Board of Regents Meeting (Flagstaff). 1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Governorship; Arizona State Capitol Building. undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Governorship; Arizona State Seal (Patricia Castro). 1976 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Governorship; Bill Signings. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Governorship; Carter, Jimmy. 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11-12)
    - Governorship; Carter-Mondale Inauguration. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Governorship; Capitol Hill Decorations. 1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Governorship; Castro for Governor Campaign. undated (Box 17, Folder 15-17)
    - Governorship; Castro for Governor Campaign. 1974 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Governorship; Castro for Governor Campaign (Speech at Nogales High School). 1970 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Governorship; Castro, Patricia (Motorcycle Accident). 1976 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Governorship; CB Radio in Governor's Limousine. undated (Box 17, Folder 21-22)
    - Governorship; Chauncey House (Governor's Residence). undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Governorship; Colorado River Tubing Trip (Parker, Arizona). undated (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
    - Governorship; Copper License Plate. 1976 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Governorship; County Attorneys' and Sheriffs' Conference (DeConcini, Dennis). 1975 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Governorship; Democratic National Convention (Castro, Raul). 1976 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Governorship; Department of Navy (Port Hueneme, California). 1977 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Governorship; "Gauntlet" (Film) Reception in Phoenix (Eastwood, Clint). 1977 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Governorship; General. undated (Box 17, Folder 31-32)
    - Governorship; General. undated (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
    - Governorship; General. 1970-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Governorship; Governor's House Savings Bond Breakfast. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Governorship; Hampton, Lionel. undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Governorship; Havasupai: Indian Reservation. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Governorship; Inauguration. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Governorship; Jaro, Sue (Special Assistant to Patricia Castro). undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Governorship; Johnson, Lady Bird. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Governorship; Kimball, Spencer W. (LDS Church President). undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Governorship; Lord Mayor of London. 1976 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Governorship; MacDonald, Peter (Navajo Nation President). undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Governorship; New York Migrant Tutorial Education Outreach Network. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Governorship; "Oregon Trail" Film Location Visit. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Governorship; Owens, Jesse. undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Governorship; Phoenix Kiwanis Club Speech. undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Governorship; Phoenix Little League All-Stars (Mexico City Tournament). 1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Governorship; Portraits (Castro, Patricia). undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Governorship; Portraits (Castro, Raul H.). undated (Box 18, Folder 24-26)
    - Governorship; Portraits (Castro, Raul H.). 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Governorship; President Neimari of Sudan. 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Governorship; Presidential Seal (Patricia Castro). undated (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Governorship; Puerto Peñasco, Mexico. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Governorship; Rhodes, John (U.S. Congressman from Arizona). 1976 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Governorship; Rotary Club of Phoenix Speech. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Governorship; Rudd, Eldon ( U.S. Congressman). 1977 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Governorship; Sacramento City College Speech. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Governorship; Sarabia, Johnny "Del Rey". 1975-1977 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Governorship; South Mountain Club Jamboree (Castro, Patricia). 1976 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Governorship; Swanson, Ray (Western Artist). 1975 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Governorship; Taiwan Visit. 1975 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Governorship; Tank Battalion Training at Ft. Huachuca (Castro, Raul). 1977 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Governorship; Time Capsule. 1977 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Governorship; Udall, Mo. 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Governorship. U.S.S. Arizona Memorial Dedication. 1976 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous; Antique Home Furnishings. undated (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous; Architecture. undated (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous; Camp Encounter. 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous; Desert Property. 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous; Dogs. undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous; Dogs. 1960-1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous; Everett, Chris. undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous; Fairway Drive. undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous; Fiestas Patrias de Douglas, Arizona. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous; Heston, Charlton. undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous; Hispanic Week (Ft Huachuca, Arizona). 1993 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous; Horses. undated (Box 19, Folder 10-13)
    - Miscellaneous; Horses. 1943-1978 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous; Humane Society Annual Meeting (Salt Lake City). 1972 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous; Indian Jewelry. undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous; Land Plot (City of Nogales, Arizona). 2003 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous; Medals. undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous; Morris the Cat. undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous; Salt River Project Event. undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous; Scottsdale Resort Suites Groundbreaking (Drinkwater, Herb). 1987 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous; South American Native Tribal Members. undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous; Space Shuttle Enterprise and Crew. undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous; Warner, Tom. undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous. World Trade Center. undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous; U.S.S. Inchon undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Subseries: Negatives, 1977
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; Andes Village Scenes. undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Ambassadorships- Argentina; General. undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Ambassadorships- El Salvador; General. undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Family Photographs; Castro Birthplace. undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Family Photographs; Castro, Raul. undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Governorship; "Castro for Governor" Campaign. undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Governorship; Christmas Decorations. undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Governorship; Governor House Savings Bond Breakfast. 1977 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Subseries: Slides, 1976
    - U.S.S. Arizona Memorial Dedication Brunch and Banquet. 1976 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - U.S.S. Arizona Memorial Dedication/Staff Christmas Party/Certosimo Party. 1976 (Box 19, Folder 36)
- Series 8: Audiovisual Material, 1973-2006
  1.0 linear foot (about 1,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  This series includes video (VHS, reel-to-reel, and DVD) and audio (cassette, reel-to-reel, and CD). Of particular interest is the 2006 video commemorating the diamond jubilee of the Cochise County Courthouse (Raul H. Castro was naturalized as a U.S. citizen at this courthouse) as well as the 1975 video of NBC's Today show highlighting the state of Arizona and including Hugh Downs's interview of Governor Raul H. Castro. Some items are in Spanish.
  - Great Moments from the Indy 500. LP. 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lic. Raul Castro y Ernesto. Audio tape: Reel-to-reel. Compact Disc. 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Northern New Mexico Children's Choir. LP. 1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "The Open Door": Legal Residency and Citizenship for you. Audio Cassette tapes (6). Compact Discs (3). 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Un Siglo de Musica Vernacula Jalisciense. LP 1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified. Audio tape: Reel-to-reel. undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Cochise County Courthouse Diamond Jubilee, 1931-2006DVD 2006 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Sesenta Minutos": Interview with Ambassador Castro, Broadcast March 17, 1980 (Channel 7), Buenos Aires. Videotape: Reel-to-reel. 1980 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - "Today" NBC's Bicentennial Salute to Arizona, September 19, 1975. Videotape: VHS (2). DVD (2). 1975 (Box 21, Folder 3-5)
- Series 9: Objects, 1964-1980
  2.5 linear feet (about 2,250 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  This series contains an assortment of plaques, campaign buttons, a key to an Argentine city, a silk pennant from Argentina, and a "Gubernatorial Decision-Maker" machine fashioned by employees at Honeywell and given to Raul Castro during his tenure as governor. (Note: some oversized objects are located in Series 11: Oversized).
  - Campaign Buttons; "Castro: Arizona's Next Governor." undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Buttons; Navajo Nation Election. undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous; Commemorative Key to City (Cuidad de Cordoba, Argentina). 1978 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous; Honeywell's Gubernatorial Decision Maker. undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Pennant; "Quilmes A.C. 1887 Argentina". undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Plaques; General. undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Series 10: Scrapbooks 1973-1977 (bulk undated)
  2.0 linear feet (about 2,000 items). Arrangement: alphabetical.
  This series includes a scrapbook of news clippings regarding the 1974 gubernatorial campaign, a scrapbook of Raul H. Castro's school and sports news clippings, Patricia Castro's high school scrapbook, Patricia Castro's Arizona first lady press clippings, and a travel scrapbook for Veronica Steiner (Raul H. Castro's mother-in-law). Some items are in Spanish.
  - 1974 Gubernatorial Election Clippings. 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Castro, Patricia. undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Castro, Patricia Norris. undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Castro, Raul (School and Sports Clippings). undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - "Excelentisimo Raul H. Castro Gobernador Estado de Arizona Mexico D.F. Mayo 1975." 1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - "Mrs. Raul H. Castro Press Clippings." undated (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
  - "Pat Castro- Alpha Chi Esawi." 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - State Corrections Department. 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - State Election. undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Steiner, Patricia. undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Steiner, Veronica. undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Series 11: Oversized 1903-2007 (bulk 1958-2007)
  6.0 linear feet (about 4,000 items).
  Arrangement: alphabetical. Included in this series are oversized items from biographical files (1995 proclamation from Governor Janet Napolitano commemorating Raul H. Castro's 89th birthday; various certificates and awards); miscellaneous (drawings, maps, political cartoons, and posters); news clippings (including 1903 issues of Arizona Republican and Tucson Citizen); subject files (blueprints for reception room at Arizona State Capitol); photographic material (including inscribed President Lyndon B. Johnson family portrait and Carter/Mondale inaugural photograph signed by President Jimmy Carter); and objects (oil portrait, plaques, Castro & Zipf law firm sign). Some items are in Spanish.
  - Biographical Files; Certificates and Awards, Miscellaneous. 1958-1991 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Files; Governor Napolitano's Proclamation in Celebration of Raul Castro's 89th Birthday. 2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - News Clippings; General. 1903 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - News Clippings; General. 1960-2007 (Box 27, Folder 4)